good afternoon, I’m
добрый день я
asking people from Russia how you feel
у людей из россии спрашиваю как вы
about Ukraine, I’m generally
относитесь к вынем украине я вообще к
negative about water if you think
воде отрицательно если вы считаете что
that your state sent troops into
то что ваше государство ввела войска в
Ukraine it was wrong for the
украину это было неправильно
war, I’m against the war,
войне это считать я против войны
well, that is, it was right
ну то есть правильно неправильно сделал
that the state did the wrong thing that led the troops  it was right not to pour it on the
государства что вело войска на
territory of another state
территорию другого государства правильно
at all,
был вообще не выливать
that is, it was wrong
то есть неправильно сделал
because most of your people
потому что большинство ваших людей
somehow under different sauces but
как-то под разными соусами но
support this war and but we have already been
поддерживает эту войну и но нам уже
bitten by salt from the TVs you, but
укушена соли с телевизоров вы а вот вы
you, too, this is the same TV that is
вы тоже это самый телевизор тот самый
turned on you  but I don’t watch those peak gifts,
turned у вас но не смотрю те пик дар ну
well, look, I talked to the girl on the
вот смотрите вот я с девушкой общался на
same, I was able to read the telegram channel there,
тоже я смог там читаю телеграм-канал в у
she has a completely different view in her head, which is
нее абсолютно другой вид в голове вот
why, even if our Ukrainian European is shorter, it’s
почему так пусть и короче наши
different between why it turns out to be
иное между почему так получается чтобы
the same  country here you are and how you
одной и той же стране вот вы и как
read the Internet and you have one position from
читайте интернет и вас одна позиция от
there are people who readers are preparing them for
есть люди которые читатели готовим их за
war for war replacement it all depends  from the
войну за войну замену это все зависит от
source where they get this
источника откуда они берут эту
information about how how do you choose the
информацию о как как вот вы выбираете
source from where to get for example
источник откуда брать например
I know I don’t believe
знаю я не верю
I don’t know how I clean it but like this
я не знаю как я убираю но вот так
it can just turn out here I’m like
она может тут просто получается я вот
this on the contrary what if we really are
так наоборот а вдруг мы действительно
there we have fascists here so you  they chose the
там у нас тут фашисты так вы выбрали не
wrong source,
тот источник
maybe the majority may or may not,
может на может и нет
because you start stubbornly
большинство так как начинает упорото
proving and here we have fascism here,
доказываешь и у нас тут фашизм у нас тут
he saves us at the net in the local forest, and you
он спасает у сетки в лес местной а вы
yourself are from which region of Russia
сами из какого региона россии
to convince the seminar I have a girl who
убедить семинара у меня девушка одна
stimulated me not there, too, and
стиме не там тоже рассказывал и
I  from ukraine khmelnytsky city is somewhere in the
я из украины хмельницкий город где то
middle between it
посредине между его
so it’s clear
так что понятно
on there aunt she has someone fighting in
на там тетенька она у нее кто-то воюет в
ukraine from relatives on so
украине из родственников на так
heaped on me but we have a fascist for our
наваливал а мне ж у нас фашист у нас для
ear to have only you agree
уха до есть только у вас согласитесь
also brut lie in what  sense and that with and the
тоже брут врут в каком смысле и что с и
world is lying not all information is true that,
мир врут не вся информация правдивая что
well, for example,
ну например
there is a lot of what there,
там много какой там
well, from not just a channel from we are talking there,
ну от не просто канал от мы говорим там
not all information is true, so this is not
не вся информация правдивая так это не о
what we are talking about, for example, our deceit and
чем вот мы например наши обману и
let’s say something
допустим что то то то
specific, that’s what our people are raping, I
конкретно вот что наши насилуют я вот в
don’t look at this door, as it were, here’s
этой дверью не смотрите как бы тут вот в
the problem, it’s clear that
чем проблема ясно что
there’s no such noise there, they gave the order there and the
шум нет такого там отдали приказ там и
wild ones rape Ukrainian women like that, but
дикие насилуйте украинских женщин так но
you yourself understand what kind of type is outside the window
вы сами понимаете какое там за окном
in the army  it’s gaining these hammered
типаж в армии набирает вот этих забитых
hearts from you, not from us in the form of our army in a
сердца у вас не у нас в виде у нас армия
completely different way, how to build,
совсем по-другому как бы построить
well, okay, giving you two, let’s say, but it
ну окей дав два тебя допустим но
turns out that your
получается суть в том что ваша ваши
troops were standing there like that in this [ __ ] cooper
войска там стояли так в это ебучее купер
on and there’s already, as it were  and video and
на и есть уже как бы и видео и
international experts will also call for a
международные эксперты тоже призовут
video I didn’t see I didn’t see it with a drone,
видео не видел не видел с дроном
for example, there was a shooting and there was already lying,
например была съемка и тут уже лежал
for example, in this during the occupation, so
например в этом во время оккупации так
above and on the street when ours had already liberated
над и улице когда уже наши освободили
you, there was the same thing, that is, a bunch of such
вам там же самое был то есть куча таких
things that
вещей которые
this is not the 20th century  now
это не 20 столетии сейчас технологии у
we have technology here you
нас тут вы
will not earn,
заработаете
but if, well, a lot of girls
не но если ну очень много девушек до
apply to the authority and if you believe it is
обращается в орган и если верить а
unknown to believe them,
неизвестно верить им
well, here it is, so to speak, if there is, but
ну и тут так сказать он если есть но
certain forensic examinations, but it’s
определенные судмедэкспертизы а
good with  Look, for example, it turns out that
хорошо смотрите например получается что
you are here that they bring refugees from
вас есть вот что привозят беженцев с
Ukraine in Tyumen,
украины в тюмене
not a single one of them, because they tell me
ни одного ней потому что мне говорят
some
некоторые
characters in a whisper from Mariupol take
персонажи шёпотом из мариуполя увозят
refugees there to them as a city, but although this
там к ним городом беженцев но хотя этот
one deports you get people in the annals, maybe they bring them somewhere I won’t
может они куда-то их привозят я не
meet  this is not there, but in tyumen it’s
встреть этого нет а в тюмени это
how big a city where the
насколько большой город ского котором
population is a
населения
million million, and even if a small
миллион миллион да и то если небольшой
town everyone knows about it, a million loves
городок этом все знают о миллион любит
Kai everyone lives his own
кая каждый живет своим
but change his life to
но смене своей жизнью до
so well then all thanks to you for
так хорошо тогда все спасибо вам за
less than 600 will end when everyone
менее 600 закончится когда вот все
asks when  no one
спрашивает когда закончится никто не
knows when it will end
знает когда закончится
because of you in your country it won’t be enough
силу вас в вашей страны не хватит
to fight for so long mushrooms help us the
воевать так долго нам помогает грибы
whole world, but the fact is that I’m taking it out
весь мир но дело в том что я сношу она
it won’t end here in a day for two or three weeks,
не закончится тут за день два три недели
that is, this conflict will drag on
то есть этот конфликт будет тянуться
debts, that is, it is in different  degree well, I
долгах то есть он в разных степень ну я
don’t have a military-political expert there,
не есть там военно-политические эксперт
but in my opinion it’s to whom the cotton opinion
но по моему это кому хлоп скому мнению
this will not end quickly, that is, she
это быстро не закончится то есть она
it will flow in different forms,
будет в разных формах перетекать
let’s say different forms of intensity,
скажем разной формы интенсивности вот
for example, ours has already been pushed back from Kharkov,
например нашей уже от харькова оттеснили
so you had distant news in the news,
вот у вас было в новостях дальние
that is, now they also liberated this
то есть сейчас тоже освободили эту
territory around Kharkov, but it remains
территорию вокруг харькова но остается
in
на
the Donetsk direction in Mariupol in
на донецком направлении на мариуполе на
Kherson I teach a lot of your troops,
херсонском учу очень много ваших войск
so this is  it won’t resolve in a day or two you
так что это она за день-два не
need a youtube channel 10 hours youtube
надо youtube канала 10 часов youtube
channel you need to run your own and what will happen if I
канал надо вести свой а что будет если я
start running my youtube channel
начну вести свои youtube канал
well on this
ну на этом у
we have people run a youtube channel
нас короче есть люди ведут youtube канал
they are good at communicating politely
у них хорошо получается вежливо общаться
here you and your neck too  and if I start
вот вам тоже тебя и шеи и если я начну
running a youtube channel, people started watching
вести youtube канал люди начали смотреть
it,
это
but what’s the point of people watching how two people are
ну а смысл людям смотреть как двух людей
talking, it doesn’t make sense that through
говорят вот нет смысла в том что через
chat roulette you record conversations with
чат рулетка вы записываете разговоры с
us with Russian data with yours and it’s
нами с русскими данных со своими и
interesting and post people’s opinions,
интересно и выкладываете мнение людей
do people come to watch  someone
нет ли людям заходит смотреть кто-то
begins to understand,
начинает понимать
they will come up with people will watch what, well,
придумают люди будут смотреть что ну
we just say
просто мы говорим
some read some kind of here in pairs  va
некоторые читают какой то тут у парнова
and telegram channel
и телеграм-канал
where sheer lies
где сплошное вранье
can’t be averse to listen to your
не может будет прочь послушаться ваш
conversation skin
разговор skin
interesting idea I think I’ll see
интересная идея я думаю я бы я посмотрю
if there are such channels you can have yours in full
если есть такие каналы можете свои полно
swing they could very well gain good
разгаре их могли очень набирают хорошо
about wife friend and good comments
про жену друг и комментарии хорошие
understood cool well everyone hold
понял прикольно хорошо все держитесь
on if on  quickly ended lived
если на побыстрее закончившихся жили
happily
счастливо
before injury for
до травмы не
some reason they will reduce Sasha’s channel
почему-то сведут канал саши прикольно
coolly all people can be 2000 further and
выявляется все люди может 2000 дальше и
brush two dudes are served in chat roulette
кисть два чувака подаются в чат-рулетке
six times cartoons about
шесть раз мульты про политику дождаться
politics  date rozmov chat roulette so
выехал даты розмова чат-рулетке так
love you thought the meaning you will
люблю ты думала смысл вам будете калана
sew the sea otter glory to ukraine
пришить слава украине